tytnetwork.com 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy - TYT Network

[Terms of Use](https://tytnetwork.com/terms/) | **Privacy Policy**

## General information

This policy sets out our privacy practices and explains how we handle the information we collect when you visit and use our sites, services, mobile applications, products, and content (“Services”).

## What we may collect

We collect information you provide to us (such as an email address used to register or communicate with us), and referral information.

When you use TYT Services, we may collect and store your Internet Protocol address.

When you enable Location Services, we may collect and store your location for the purposes of personalizing your app experience and enabling certain features.

When you enable Notification Services, we may collect an address for your device that allows us to send notifications to you.

## Email from TYT

Sometimes we’ll send administrative emails about account or service changes, or new policies. You can’t opt out of them. You can always opt out of non-administrative emails such as ShopTYT. We won’t email you to ask for your password or other account information. If you receive such an email, send it to us immediately.

## Disclosure of your information

As a rule, we don’t share your personal information outside the company.

We won’t sell your personal information.

We may share your personal information with third parties in limited circumstances, including: (1) with your consent; (2) to a vendor or partner who meets our data protection standards; or (3) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process.

If we’re going to share your information in response to legal process, we’ll give you advance notice so you can challenge it, unless we’re prohibited from doing so by law or court order. We will object to requests for information about users of our site that we believe to be improper.

## Cookies

We use cookies and similar technologies such as pixels and local storage to recognize you when you return to our Services. We do that so we can deliver you personalized content and services, and keep track of things you’ve already seen or interacted with.

Some third-party services that we use, such as Facebook Pixel or Google Analytics, may place their own cookies in your browser. This Privacy Policy covers use of cookies by TYT only and not the use of cookies by third parties.
